mexx.com 2017-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Other - Mexx.com - Fashion, Inspiration, Stores and more

If you provide us with personal data via our Website or other channels, this is done on an entirely voluntary basis and with the granting of your consent for it to be used in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. If you choose not to provide the requested information, various customer benefits may not be available and on-line functionalities on the Website may also not be available. In certain cases, only those people that have submitted the necessary personal data to us are able to use certain services and in other ways avail themselves of the activities and offers available on our Website and (mobile) application. As transparency and fair play are particularly important issues for us, we provide various options, depending on the exact circumstances, in order to help you retain control over your data. These options include the possibility to unsubscribe from services or delete user accounts or to receive information about the data held.

8.1 Right to object

E-mails that Mexx sends to you that contain for instance a newsletter or marketing content, have the option to terminate the receiving of such e-mails (unsubscribe) by following the relevant instructions in the respective e-mail. If you want to stop receiving emails from us, you can simply click on this unsubscribe hyperlink and we will stop sending our emails to you.

If you do not wish information about your behavior at our Website or (mobile) application being collected and assessed, you can opt-out of the gathering of the web analytics data as described below.

If you wish to object to receiving promotional information and offers in general, so including by regular mail, e-mail, per SMS, by telephone or by any other electronic means, or if you want to withdraw your consent, you may at any time write to Mexx Europe B.V., Johan Huizingalaan 400, 1066 JS, Amsterdam, the Netherlands, reference: data protection, or send an e-mail to [info@mexx.com](mailto:info@mexx.com). In case we have doubt about your identity, we can ask you to identify yourself (e.g. by sending a copy of your passport ID).

With regard to other types of messages you may receive, such as maintenance announcements or administrational notifications, the receiving of these can only be terminated by deleting your account, as such messages are a mandatory part of user accounts and the related use of our Website and (mobile) applications. You can have your account deleted by sending an email to [info@mexx.com](mailto:info@mexx.com).

8.2 Right to request information

You have the right to be informed at any time about the personal data stored about you, its origin and recipients as well as the purpose for which it is being stored. Information about stored personal data can be obtained by using the contact details in the Contact Information in section 14.

8.3 Right to request correction

You have the right to request to correct, supplement, delete or block the personal data stored about you. We will notify you as to whether and, if so, to what extent, we will comply with your request. If for any reason we don’t comply with your request, we will provide you with the reasons.
